[{"answer": "I can't believe you didn't check", "docId": "Crime-Spree.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Why should I have to put it on the list? It's like saying to buy a car with tires", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "There's no reason to be abusive. You're projecting your anger on me as a defense mechanism", "docId": "Crime-Spree.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "I'm talking about human beings communicating openly and honestly", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": " -- Zero isn't interested in your life story.  Who gets killed", "docId": "Crime-Spree.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": " No one? Then why is Zero here", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "I did not order escargot", "docId": "Crime-Spree.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "What kind of restaurant doesn't serve wine", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "They're gonna be what", "docId": "Crime-Spree.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Good word", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": " We have a problem. Problem isn't the right word. Dilemma. No that really doesn't describe", "docId": "Crime-Spree.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "No, that's not Mr. my friend", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "What do we do", "docId": "Crime-Spree.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Go where?   The police are outside", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": " -- you stole my cousin my friend's car", "docId": "Crime-Spree.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "He told my friend he didn't know anything about his car", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "They were all French guys", "docId": "Crime-Spree.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": " Yeah, French guys from that place", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "What do you want now", "docId": "Crime-Spree.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Man, I can get anything", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Yeah and he can't stand it that I tried to do something to better myself", "docId": "Crime-Spree.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": " Better than spending my life crawling through windows in the middle of the night", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Yeah. All set. Tomorrow morning. Ten o'clock. Room 211. Barclay Hotel on River Street. Oh, and due to your recent notoriety and the heat that comes with it, I'm going to have to increase my brokerage fee to twenty five hundred", "docId": "Crime-Spree.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "We had a deal before you and your friends became the new poster boys for crime", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "It doesn't matter where we go. Between Zammito and the that place they'll find us. We have to end this here", "docId": "Crime-Spree.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "I don't know", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Yeah. I mean besides that.    They treating you all right? Food okay", "docId": "Crime-Spree.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "I don't want anything.", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "I can get them", "docId": "Crime-Spree.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "A pass? How you gonna give me a pass? A witness can put me at the crime scene", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "A pass? How you gonna give me a pass? A witness can put me at the crime scene", "docId": "Crime-Spree.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "They don't have a murder weapon", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "You didn't have to kill my friend", "docId": "Crime-Spree.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "What about me? Aren't I a loose end", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Hey buddy, you just can't push in here", "docId": "Crime-Spree.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "I most certainly will not g", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Why do I always have to answer the phone", "docId": "Crime-Spree.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "I'm not any closer than you are", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "Anybody know about that car outside", "docId": "Crime-Spree.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "No.   It's mine", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "And I'm tellin' you it ain't! Now, turn your tac", "docId": "Crime-Spree.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "Fuck me?   Fuck you", "qsentId": 42}]